CURRICULUM VITAE

NGUYEN TUAN DUC (Mr.)

D.O.B 28.08.1991

Address 21i/13 Tran Xuan Soan street, ward Tan Hung, 7 district

Email <u>duc.ntuan@gmail.com</u>

Cell phone 0906.859.322

CAREER OBJECTIVES _____

Never hesitate to work hard to get more experiences and try my best to contribute to the company's success.

My career path is to become a Business Analyst expert in field of software technology and relevant software's solution.

Position Applied: Business Analyst.

WORKING EXPERIENCES

January, 2016 to Now: MAT BAO CORP. COMPANY

Position: Business Analyst

• Key task:

Analyst system document and analyst specific document. The projects joined:

- ✓ Enterprise resource management (ERM).
- ✓ Mat Bao's business products: domain, hosting, server, email, security web.
- ✓ Domain market system online.
- ✓ Researching about O-doo, WHMCS.
- ✓ Matbao.net version mobile.
- ✓ Digital marketing of Matbao.net
- ✓ Human resource solution
- ✓ Tele-sale management: Abbott, OMS, Lazada, Daikin.

January, 2015 to December, 2015: TAA CORP. COMPANY

- Position: Developer, Business Analyst, Deployment product
- Key task:

Joined all project which specialized in coding, deploying product of ERP solution

- ✓ Management Software GONSA Company (Pharmacy): Accounting and Finance, Sale, Inventory stock.
- ✓ Management Software Dong Nai Pharmacy Company: Accounting and Finance, Sale and Purchase, Inventory stock.



EDUCATION AND PRIZE _____

9/2011 - 12/2013: Graduating in NIIT Indian Academy - Diploma NIIT

Major: Software Engineer

9/2012 - 7/2016: Graduating in Ho Chi Minh University Food Industry - Diploma IT

• Major: Software Technology Engineer

2013: Prize Microsoft Offfice Word Champion Specialist

SPECIALIST KNOWLEDGE

- Object Oriented Programming
- .NET (C#, ASP.NET MVC, ADO.NET, LINQ)
- Algorithm and Data structure
- Analysis and Design Information System, UML.
- SQL Database Server Management
- Dev Express Tool, Power Design Tool, Axure, Visual Studio, Visio.

PROJECTS HAVE DONE _______

10/2015 – **12/2015**: The project teamwork: Communist Youth Union of HCM University Food Industry Management Software by LINQ to SQL, LINQ to Dataset.

9/2015 – 11/2015: The project teamwork: Supermarket Mobile Management Software by LINQ to SQL, LINQ to Dataset

4/2015 – 6/2015: Research and Building ID3 Algorithm to consult the choosing subject for HCM University Food Industry.

INTEREST ______

- Sharing and exchanging IT knowledge, experience.
- Researching document IT, new technology.
- Playing logic game, singing, listening.
- Team builling, go outside with friend and colleagues.

SOFT SKILLS ______

- Soft Skill Certificate: Organization and Problem Solving (by Hoa Sen University), Communication and Presentation.
- Detail and dedicated oriented
- Teamwork and leading
- Independent and ability to work under pressure
- Time management.